{
    "subject": "resource/Kinetic_Suspension_Technology",
    "predicate": "http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#comment",
    "object": "Kinetic Suspension Technology is a developer of passive vehicle suspension systems.  The company is based in Dunsborough, Western Australia.Tenneco Automotive acquired the Kinetic suspension system and safety technology with its acquisition of Kinetic Ltd, Dunsborough Western Australia in 1999.",
    "human_readable": "The comment about Kinetic Suspension Technology is that it is a developer of passive vehicle suspension systems, based in Dunsborough, Western Australia.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.93013596534729,
            "question": "Is Kinetic Suspension Technology a passive or active suspension system developer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8848868608474731,
            "question": "Kinetic Suspension Technology is based in which Australian region?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8495945930480957,
            "question": "What type of vehicle suspension systems does Kinetic Suspension Technology develop?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7915468215942383,
            "question": "What kind of technology does Kinetic Suspension Technology use?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7811196446418762,
            "question": "Name the location of Kinetic Suspension Technology's operations."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7732771039009094,
            "question": "What does Kinetic Suspension Technology specialize in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7592269778251648,
            "question": "Where is Kinetic Suspension Technology headquartered?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7549975514411926,
            "question": "Where can you find Kinetic Suspension Technology?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6918246150016785,
            "question": "In which country is Kinetic Suspension Technology located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5822321176528931,
            "question": "What is the primary function of a passive vehicle suspension system?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The comment about Kinetic Suspension Technology is that it is a developer of passive vehicle suspension systems, based in Dunsborough, Western Australia.",
            "html": "dbpedia_908_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In which country is Kinetic Suspension Technology located?",
            "html": "dbpedia_908_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where can you find Kinetic Suspension Technology?",
            "html": "dbpedia_908_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where is Kinetic Suspension Technology headquartered?",
            "html": "dbpedia_908_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_908_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_908_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_908_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_908_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_908_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_908_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_908_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_908_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_908_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_908_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\nThe documents provide information about Kinetic Pty Ltd and its development of a passive suspension system called a Kinetic system. However, they do not mention that it is based in Dunsborough, Western Australia. The note to editors mentions that Tenneco Automotive acquired the Kinetic suspension system with its acquisition of Kinetic Ltd of Australia, but it does not specify the location within Australia.\n\nThe correct information about Kinetic Pty Ltd can be found in the following statement: \"The kinetic suspension technology used in KDSS was developed by Kinetic Pty Limited, a company in Western Australia...\""
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe provided context mentions that \"Tenneco Automotive acquired the Kinetic suspension system and safety technology with its acquisition of Kinetic Ltd of Australia in 1999, an advanced suspension engineering company based in Dunsborough, Western Australia.\" This supports the statement that Kinetic Suspension Technology is a developer of passive vehicle suspension systems based in Dunsborough, Western Australia."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n     \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "Kinetic Pty Ltd was actually acquired by Tenneco Automotive, not the other way around.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}